# Roman Kholodkov

Qiryat Motzkin, Haifa, Israel



chikitonik@gmail.com



+972504694780



linkedin.com/in/roman-kholodkov

## **Summary**

Data Analyst

I have 7 years experience in IT as a SAP specialist. My new goal is to expand knowledge in the Data Science field. Currently, I am involved in online course of Yandex.practicum Data scientist (until June 2022). I'm finding a job on Data Analyst junior position to expand my skills.

Please read about me and my portfolio on https://chikitonik.github.io

Languages:

English - Upper-Intermediate

Hebrew - alef+

Russian - Native

No bad habits.

I do sports, like DIY, I am fond of programming.

Non-confrontational, responsive, punctual.

Analytical mindset, responsible.

Have driver's license

Note: I am a new immigrant, if you hire me, the absorption service will pay me part of the salary on the first year.

## **Experience**

## SAP Specialist

Armtek

Jul 2018 - Present (3 years 9 months +)

Working in the second line of SAP technical support in SD and MM modules, e-store support

Main responsibility:

- working with users requests:
  searching and fixing problems
  providing the necessary accesses
  consulting on web requests
- teaching users
- making the settings in the system for new commercial object
- replication solutions to other retail facilities
- writing instructions for users
- writing regulatory documents for users as to work in Z transactions

#### For all modules:

- skills in working with the debugger and reading ABAP code
- preparation of loaders in LSMW
- working with tables in SE16N
- creating reports in SQ01 with ABAP code
- testing new reports and programs in SAP

## SAP Specialist

### **Bezant**

Jun 2015 - Jun 2018 (3 years 1 month) Supporting and training of users in FI, MM, SD, WMS

#### For all modules:

- skills in working with the debugger and reading ABAP code
- preparation of instructions for users, keeping them up-to-date
- preparation of loaders in LSMW
- working with tables in SE16N
- organization of data transfer between SAP and other enterprise management systems
- participation in SAP implementation, organization of data migration
- testing new reports and programs in SAP

#### Additionally:

- training users in Excel skills
- writing macros for processing data in Excel (many projects, such as processing customer orders, processing invoices and packages, compiling reports, etc)
- creating SQL queries for databases
- writing small programs in JAVA for specific needs

## Key Account Manager

#### Bezant

Mar 2007 - Jun 2015 (8 years 4 months)

Sales support and analysis of the key clients as METRO Cash & Carry, Castorama, Lenta, Real

### **Education**



### Saratov State University named after N.G.Chernyshevsky

Master's degree, Geography

### **Skills**

SAP ERP • Microsoft Excel • Data Analysis • Data Science • Machine Learning • SQL • Python (Programming Language) • Pandas (Software) • Jupyter